

ABOUT ME

Creative web developer dedicated to developing and optimizing interactive, userfriendly, and feature-rich websites. Leverage analytical skills and strong attention to detail to deliver original and efficient web solutions, provide technical knowledge and expertise, build new website from start to finish.

CONTACT ME

- +639668747432
- 107 Atis St. Minane Concepcion, Tarlac 2316

FOLLOW ME

facebook.com/cadzonly

PRO SKILLS

- **HTML**
- **CSS**
- **JQUERY**
- PHP
- LARAVEL
- **WORDPRESS**
- **PHOTOSHOP**
- AFTER EFFECTS
- VISUAL BASIC
- ANGULAR/
- **VUE/REACT**
- **GIT**

WILFREDO A. CADIANG JR

Web Developer



JOB EXPERIENCES

Greatway Financial Inc

January 2022 - Present Web Developer: involves working on all aspects of a web application, from setting up the project to coding, testing, integrating the front end, managing the database,

and ensuring the application is secure and optimized for performance. Collaboration and continuous learning are also essential aspects of this role.

PTW Philippines Private Co. Ltd April 2019 - June 2022

Web Developer: Write well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices. Create website layout/user interface by using standard HTML/CSS practices. Integrate data from various back-end services and databases. Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical needs. Create and maintain software documentation. Be responsible for maintaining, expanding, and scaling our site. Stay plugged into emerging technologies/industry trends and apply them into operations and activities.

Bataan National High School - SHS October 2017 - April 2019

Teacher II: Prepares lesson plans and conducts various ICT Subjects (Computer Systems Servicing, Media Information Literacy, and Empowerment Technologies).

Colegio de San Juan de Letran – Bataan June 2014 - April 2017

Information Technology Instructor: Prepares lesson plans and conducts various Programming (Java, VB.net, C#.net, Android and Php); Computer Networking (Networking Fundamentals and Server and Client Networking); Database System (MySql and MS SQL SERVER); and Multimedia editing courses for both College and High School Department.

STI College Tarlac

June 2013 - May 2014

Laboratory Custodian: Coordinates scheduling of students and teachers for the purpose of maintaining computer lab operations and activities; Maintains computer hardware and software applications inventory for the purpose of ensuring availability of equipment and/or instructional material in computer lab; Monitors student activities while in computer lab for the purpose of maintaining a safe environment that is conducive to learning; Troubleshoots malfunctions of hardware and/or software applications for the purpose of determining appropriate actions to maintain computer lab operations; conducts various programming and networking courses.



EDUCATION

- Tarlac State University, Tarlac City Master in Information Technology (continuing, started 2nd trimester A.Y. 2014-2015, 30 Units)
- Colegio de San Juan de Letran Bataan Certificate for Professional Education, March 2015
- STI College Tarlac, Tarlac City BS in Information Technology; Academic Excellence, April 2013



WW PROJECTS

- amegahotel.com
- ptwsingapore.com
- vacationsunlimitedholidays.com
- sicp.ust-iics.net

- amegaresidences.com
- amegavacations.com
- myonlineoffice.greatwayfinancial.com
- phoenix.greatwayfinancial.com



REFERENCE

Upon Request